<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>overview on Historial Land Conflict</title>
    <link>/tags/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in overview on Historial Land Conflict</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>1. General Overview</title>
      <link>/method/1.-general-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/method/1.-general-overview/</guid>
      <description>The goal is to establish which African tribal groups have moved/changed since 1800. Pre-colonial tribe names are determined by the Murdock Map of Ethnic Boundaries (1956), which refers to the location of the groups in 1800. Current tribe names come from the GREG data set (2010), which refers to the location of the groups in 1960.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Matching Procedure</title>
      <link>/method/2.-matching-procedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/method/2.-matching-procedure/</guid>
      <description>For this classification we used as the main source the classification of tribes provided in Murdock (1969). In Murdock, each tribe is associated to a tribe number y within a chapter x so that its code is x:y. In most cases, the chapter is equivalent to a culture family encompassing a number of tribes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Cleaning Procedure</title>
      <link>/method/3.-cleaning-procedure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/method/3.-cleaning-procedure/</guid>
      <description>As both Murdock and GREG geo-databases were manually recovered from historical maps, many measurement errors might exist due to the geo-referencing process. For instance: (i) polygons borders could be miss-located due to manual process, (ii) There must be complex geometries that cannot be intersect with other polygons, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1. Main Results</title>
      <link>/overall-results/1.-overall-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overall-results/1.-overall-results/</guid>
      <description>In general, we found that 59% of the geographical area belong to Similar tribes of Murdock and Greg (27% of total intersections).
           Classification of Murdock-GREG Intersections    For those tribes that are Similar/Equivalent we analyze the level of its relation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Why Change</title>
      <link>/overall-results/2.-why-differents/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/overall-results/2.-why-differents/</guid>
      <description>Establishing the reason why a specific geographical area is considered a homeland of two different tribes in Murdock and GREG is not always straightforward. We initially collect information from three main sources: (i) Wikipedia, (ii) eHRAF World Cultures , and (iii) country-specific books.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>